

Ajmal.VpWeb Developer

ABOUT ME:

Hi! My name is Ajmal. I am a Web Developer, and I'm very passionate and dedicated to my work. With 1 years experience as a professional Web developer, I have acquired the skills and knowledge necessary to make your project a success. I enjoy every step of the design process, from discussion and collaboration.

CONTACT ME



+91 8136825349



ajmalaju5758559@gmail.com



Kodur Malappuram,Kerala,India P O Kodur 676504

SOCIAL LINKS



www.facebook/profile/ajmal.vp.5076



www.linkedin.com/in/ajmal-vp-4108861b1



ajmal_aju_vp

ACADEMIC EDUCATION:

Corono Destroyed Everthing:(

2020....

Bachelor of Arts

2019 - 2020 Studying BCA(University Of Calicut)

Higher Secondary

2017 - 2019 AM HSS

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION:

Web Development

In order to make the server, application, and database communicate with each other, back-end devs use server-side languages like

Web Design

front-end devs must be adept at three main languages: HTML, CSS, and Javascript programming

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Backend Developer

2020....

In order to make the server, application, and database communicate with each other, back-end devs use server-side languages like

Frontend Developer

2019 - 2020

front-end devs must be adept at three main languages: HTML, CSS, and Javascript programming

Graphic Designer

2017 - 2019

Print Brochures & Newsletters Logos & Business Cards Posters & Post Cards Stationery PHOTOGRAPHY Black & White

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS:

Web Design:
Web Development:
Networking:
Graphic Design:
Content Writing: